Guide to the Gail and Stephen Rudin American presidential collection, 1775-2009.
Rudin, Gail and Stephen American presidential collection
- Series II. Other U.S. presidents
  - Wilson, Woodrow Office held: "As Professor of Law and Politics, Princeton University" Addressee: Frank Walter Brooks Writer's location: "Judd Haven, Ontario, Canada", September 11, 1900; Pages: 3 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    On the Constitution as a living document. Included with this letter is correspondence regarding its possible sale to Thomas Madigan in 1936. Madigan was a well known autograph dealer of his day who wrote a book titled "Word Shadows of the Great".
    Rudin # P-197
  - Wilson, Woodrow Office held: As President Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", March 1916; Pages: 2 1/2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    In the wake of Pershing's pursuit of Pancho Villa, Wilson tries to manage the press. From the Forbes Collection - Part One.
    Rudin # P-198
  - Wilson, Woodrow Office held: As President Writer's location: "The White House Washington, D.C.", January 29, 1917; Pages: 3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Vote of the Immigration Bill. H.R. 10384.
    Rudin # P-199
  - Wilson, Woodrow Office held: As President Addressee: "Clarence Dillon, War Industries Board " Writer's location: Washington, D.C., September 6, 1919; Pages: 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    First "dollar a year men" check. Countersigned by Bernard Baruch.
    Rudin # P-200
  - Wilson, Woodrow Office held: As ex-President Addressee: "Eleanor Wilson McAdoo (Wilson's Daughter)" Writer's location: Washington, D.C., December 18, 1922; Pages: 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    "In spite of breakdown and political persecution, I realize that I am the most fortunate man in the world".
    Rudin # P-201
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Signed Books
Keeping Faith: Memoirs of a President, by Jimmy Carter, 1982.
A Time to Heal, by Gerald Ford, 1979.
No More Vietnams, by Richard Nixon. 2 copies, one unsigned.
The Audacity of Hope, by Barack Obama.
Report of the Commissioner of Patents for the year 1849, Office of Printers to the Senate. Contains patent listing for Abraham Lincoln.